<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kelvinkoon.dev</title><link>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on kelvinkoon.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kelvinkoon.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building babiri.net</title><link>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/posts/building_babiri/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/posts/building_babiri/</guid><description>Prologue After 2 months and 132 commits, babiri V2&amp;rsquo;s API has been launched! babiri is comprised of an API for aggregated usage stats gathered from Pokémon Showdown replays. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly excited to share how babiri came to be, why it exists, and the technology powering the project. This post is also inspired by Kevin&amp;rsquo;s zeal.gg write-up, which is a fantastic read on another competitive gaming tool.
A Children&amp;rsquo;s Game In 2005, I received a copy of Pokémon Emerald for the Nintendo Game Boy.</description></item><item><title>An ECE Electives Review</title><link>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/posts/ubc-ece-electives/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/posts/ubc-ece-electives/</guid><description>Prologue UBC&amp;rsquo;s Electrical and Computer Engineering department offers no shortage of advanced electives for upper year students. As someone who has a tendency to like too many things, I&amp;rsquo;ve worried about fitting all my interests into 12 credits. Though I ended up taking more credits than needed, the opportunity to dive into new fields was invaluable to my learning.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be going over the advanced electives I took to hopefully help you decide which electives may (or may not) be suitable for you.</description></item><item><title>LeetCode Intro Guide</title><link>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/posts/leetcode-intro-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kelvinkoon.github.io/posts/leetcode-intro-guide/</guid><description>Prologue The guide you are reading assumes you have taken CPSC259 if you are in ELEC or CPSC221 if you are in CPEN / CPSC, which are the introductory Data Structures and Algorithms (DS/A) courses offered at UBC. Although CPSC259 is less in-depth compared to CPSC221, the deficiencies can be remedied through practice. Even if you have not taken either course, the article can still provide take-aways to the current state of interviews.</description></item></channel></rss>